BRADY COLLIER

LEAVENWORTH, WA, UNITED STATES

PHONE 509-264-3196

EMAIL bradycollier.123@gmail.com

SUMARY

I carry over 10 years of successful customer service relationship building, technical skills, and project coordination in a fast paced environment. I'm a graduate of the University of Washington with a bachelor's degree in economics. Education is important to me, so I continued my education and I have recently graduated from the full-stack coding bootcamp at the same university, gaining valuable skills such as project management, front end development, back end development, and database management.

EXPERIENCE

Amazon

Seattle, WA // Kuiper Recruiting Coordinator (contract) // 07/2022 – 11/2022

- Track recruiting activities and providing candidate status in a weekly report.
- Schedule interviews and phone screens working directly with candidates, hiring managers, executive assistants, and directors.
- Provide follow-up correspondence to candidates on recruiting status via phone and email.
- Coordinate the post-interview debrief meetings and providing debrief materials.
- Identify opportunities for improving candidate experience and scheduling efficiency.

Icicle Ridge Winery Peshastin, WA // Sales Engineer & Events // 08/2013 – present

- Build sustainable relationships with guests and members, leading the team in new wine club signups.
- Utilize knowledge of the industry to answer wine questions and educate clientele.
- Grew revenue 70% year to year during the pandemic, despite shutdowns and limited capacity.
- Assist with wine making, moving inventory, and general maintenance.

Safe Streets NGO

Tacoma, WA // Board of Directors Intern // 01/2019 – 07/2020

- Attended and participated in board meetings discussing financials, growth, and organizational planning.
- Lobbied for successful state funding, making cold calls to politicians and voters gathering support.
- Brought in needed fundraising and gifting for the organization.
- Developed the board and CEO a "best practices" presentation, creating leadership principles followed to utilize for organizational improvements.

American Red Cross

Leavenworth, WA // Event Coordinator // 01/2015 – 04/2015

Coordinated and organized event with volunteer hiring, advertisement, and setup.

EDUCATION

University of Washington

Full Stack Coding Bootcamp // 2022 - 2023 Project manager for all three group projects

University of Washington

Bachelor of Arts: Economics // 2018 – 2021

SKILLS

- Project management
- **JavaScript**
- HTML5
- CSS
- MvSQL
- MERN Stack (React.js, Express.js, MongoDB, Node.js